"Sava the class clown"
Umm
Depended on the class, actually.
Depends on the class, sometimes I was the class clown.
We were reading Macbeth
And I did silly voices every time we read it.
And this one, like, popular guy in the class
I was playing an old dude so I did
I did a voice like this when I voiced him
And my teacher didn't care, he thought it was funny
But this one boy in the class was like
Oh my GOD, can you be normal for once?!
And I was just like
WHY?
Huh?
What, you got a prob-
And I actually like, I con-
I confronted- I just said like
"What, what's the problem with me reading?"
"Like, are you guys, is it-"
"Is it physically hurting you?"
"For me to do an old man voice for the old man character?"
And I was like "Sorry sorry, I'll read it normal this time".
"I'll read it normal this time."
And then I read it and I was like
I was like "Oh no, what ever shall I do?"
This is exactly how I read it.
I read it like that after he did that.
God, can you be normal for once?
No, can you...
I don't know, can you...
...die?