I wanna address this one.
This one, I saw and
it's been haunting my- I- my brain
ever since I've seen it.
Listen.
When you say "deli wipe", though
I- wouldn't it-
I would think it would be like
a slice of like cold cut turkey
and not- and not, uhh, bread.
I'm- I-
Have I done that with turkey bef-
No...
No, I haven't done it with turkey before...
BUT!
A deli...
It would make more sense if it was turkey, that's all I'm sayin'
Should I try a deli wipe, guys?
Should I try-
Should I try eating a deli wipe?
"Yes."
"No!"
"NO!"
What do you-
Why not!?
Why can't-
"No"?
"No", you don't want me to eat a deli wipe?
Alright, if you guys say no, I won't do it.
I won't, I w-
I- I won't...
do it...
...right?
Yeah?
"No", okay...
I...
...will not...
I should make a short
where I make a deli wipe and eat it!
Let's go!
I'm gonna do that.
I'm gonna make a short where I make a deli wipe and then eat it.
Yeah.
I'm gonna handcam it.
I'm gonna record my hand
with my phone, of me
deli wiping up the counters
and then...
consuming it.